

# **Full Stack Developer**

Phone (520) 709-1298

Email: art a henry@yahoo.com

Website: https://arthur-portfolio

Linkedin: linkedin.com/arthur-henry-contact info

Address: 43469 West Caven Drive Maricopa, AZ. 85138

### Summary

As a software developer my responsibilities vary from day-to-day, allowing for a wide variety of experiences and challenges from project-to-project. I'm able to provide best business practice for design, development and execution of software solutions.

### Core Competencies

JavaScript AWS HTML5 CSS3 JAVA Rest API Angular React MongoDB Maven NodeJS MySQL

## Professional Experience

ELPHA, San Francisco,

August 2020 – Present

# CA. Full Stack Developer

- Deploy Spring Boot applications using Elastic Beanstalk and AWS CICD tools.
- Work with business analyst to understand the business models and goals.
- Optimized company's compliant handling, reducing boilerplate code and creating highly efficient application.
- Connect Restful Services API for interfacing server side logic with front end user interface using, HTML5,
   CSS3, and modern JavaScript to develop interactive and responsive websites.
- Use React framework to create single page application (SPA) that binds data to specific views and synchronize data.

HEWLETT PACKARD, Phoenix, AZ.

June 2017 – August 2020

### Front End Developer

- Develop a customer support platform, using Angular.
- Understanding Angular component logic, and developing a layout of an application.
- Create SPA's for login for main page containing favorites and page for continuous integration configuration.
- Build and execute a brand new customer resolution management tool using Angular and Java to
  efficiently monitor, encode, and resolve customer questions and concerns.
- Work with payment team to save over 50,000 customers time and improve cash flow through development of modern, responsive customer experience.

SPRINT-PARANET, Chicago, IL.

Senior Software Engineer

March 2013 - June 2017

- Work with engineering managers to develop and improve world-class coding standards, design patterns.
- Build applications with reliability and scalability to meet customer demands.
- Develop, document, test, and debug new and existing software systems and applications.
- Modify HTML, JavaScript, and CSS web pages to optimize the page's performance for faster loading and browsing.
- Worked in a team environment to develop and maintain business solutions to increase profits through adopting an Agile approach.

Education

**Keller Graduate School of Management**Master Degree

Master's in Computer Information Systems June 2016 to August 2018 **DeVry University** Bachelor Degree

Bachelor's in Computer Science March 2011 to June 2015